▍2026 美网 男单决赛
兹维列夫 6-3 7-6² 5-7 6-2 谢尔顿 · 赛后场上采访
We'd like to invite our finalist, Ben Shelton,
有请我们的亚军 谢尔顿
to come on stage.
请他上台
Congratulations, Ben.
恭喜你 谢尔顿
You've had an amazing two weeks here.
这两周你打得非常出色
Congratulations on making your first
恭喜你打进第一个大满贯决赛
and certainly not your last major final.
而这肯定不会是最后一个
We'd love to hear your thoughts.
说说你此刻的感受
Yeah.
嗯
Well, first first and most importantly,
首先 最重要的一件事
I want to thank God.
我要感谢上帝
My successes are a gift,
我的成功是礼物
the failures are a gift,
失败也是礼物
and being here playing in front
能站在你们面前
of you guys is a gift.
打球 也是礼物
Sasha,
萨沙
congrats on on these two weeks, man.
恭喜你这两周 兄弟
Your second Grand Slam title,
你的第二个大满贯冠军
two in one year.
一年里拿了两个
You, you're one of the very best players
你是世界上最顶尖的球员之一
in the world, maybe the best player
也许就是今年
in the world this year.
全世界最好的那一个
What you're doing is incredible.
你做到的事情不可思议
The way you're serving,
你的发球
the way you're moving and playing.
你的移动和打法
You work harder than anyone I know.
你比我认识的任何人都努力
You put more hours on the court
你在球场上花的时间
than anyone I know.
比我认识的任何人都多
You and your team
你和你的团队
do things the right way.
用对的方式做事
And sincerely happy for you guys
我真心为你们高兴
to to hold this title.
能捧起这座奖杯
It's been a long time coming here.
这一天等了很久
I want to thank my team.
我要感谢我的团队
I have I got the best support team
我拥有这一行
in the business.
最好的后援团队
you know to do this with my family by
能有家人在身边
my side.
一起走到这一步
These four guys over here
这边这四个人
who dedicate their life
把他们的人生
to my career spending time traveling
投进了我的职业生涯
the world with me.
陪我走遍世界
It's an unmatched level of commitment.
这种投入无人能比
I appreciate you guys to my squad
谢谢你们 还有我的伙伴们
over here in this corner.
就坐在这个角落
Every one of you guys are so special
你们每一个人都很特别
in your own way.
各有各的特别
You guys showed up to to support me,
你们来支持我
have showed up to support me every day
我职业生涯的每一天
of my career.
一天都没缺席
I appreciate you guys.
谢谢你们
Love you guys.
爱你们
To the USA,
致美网
you guys have done it again.
你们又做到了
Put put together an amazing tournament.
办了一届了不起的大赛
My favorite tournament of the year.
我一年里最喜欢的赛事
the greatest tournament in the world.
世界上最伟大的赛事
Craig, the new CEO,
新任首席执行官克雷格
congratulations on the new position.
恭喜你上任
You've changed this game in many ways
你在很多方面改变了这项运动
and you're just getting started.
而你才刚刚开始
We're so happy to have you
有你在我们很高兴
and thanks for everything
也谢谢你
that you've done here already.
已经为这里做的一切
Eric, tournament director, thank you as well.
赛事总监埃里克 也谢谢你
your guys commitment to Americans
你们对美国球员的投入
American success running
对美国网球的付出
this tournament to to to be the greatest
把这项赛事办成
in the world is is unbelievable.
世界第一 难以置信
So, thank you all everyone at the USA.
谢谢美网的每一个人
I want
我要谢谢
to thank the sponsors all the sponsors
所有赞助商
for making this tournament possible,
是他们让这项赛事办得起来
all the volunteers, the drivers, my driver,
所有志愿者 司机们
my driver Xavier is up there somewhere.
我的司机泽维尔就在那边
I appreciate you X.
谢谢你 X
You're the man.
你最棒
To the umpires, ball kids, everyone
还有裁判 球童
at the practice desk, all the security guards
练习场的工作人员 保安
who make me smile every day.
他们每天都让我微笑
This this is is my happy place.
这里是让我开心的地方
This is the place that I I love to spend time
我最喜欢待在这儿
and I wish this tournament never ended.
真希望这项赛事永远不结束
So, thank you all.
所以 谢谢大家
I want to thank my sponsors,
我要感谢我的赞助商
everyone behind the scenes
所有幕后的人
who supported me along the way,
一路支持我
believed in me.
相信我的人
We still have a long way to go,
我们还有很长的路要走
but I'm very appreciative of everyone who's
但我非常感激
had my back from the beginning.
从一开始就挺我的人
And lastly, to the city of New York,
最后 致纽约这座城市
to the to the fans who showed up today,
致今天到场的球迷
the fans at home,
屏幕前的球迷
the people who've been here all week,
这一整周都在这儿的人
the people who stayed till 4 in the morning.
还有熬到凌晨四点的人
You guys drove me.
是你们推着我往前
You guys brought me to the place
是你们把我带到今天
that I'm here today, the position
带到我想要的位置
that I want to be in in the finals
站在这些大赛
of these tournaments.
决赛的赛场
I'm just getting started
我才刚刚开始
and I'll be back here again.
我还会回到这里
Thank you so much.
非常感谢大家